export const GeneralFAQs = [
  {
    question: "What are your gym's opening hours?",
    answer: "Our gym is open from Sunday to Sunday, from 5 am – 10 pm.",
  },
  {
    question: "Where is your gym located?",
    answer:
      "We currently have 2 branches, one in Bole and one in Sarbet. Bole Branch – Bole Medhanialem near Sheger Building Sarbet Branch – Sarbet Bisrate Gebreil near South African Embassy.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you offer a trial membership or day passes?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we offer day pass options. Please refer to our Services section to learn more.",
  },
  {
    question: "What types of equipment do you have available?",
    answer:
      "At our gym, performance is our primary focus, with a strong emphasis on free-weight exercises. Our equipment includes barbells, bumper plates, kettlebells, dumbbells, wall balls, slam balls, heavy bags, and sleds. Additionally, we offer a variety of cardio options such as air bikes, rowing machines, and ski ergs, along with strength machines to cater to all fitness levels and goals.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I bring a guest to the gym?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can. If you’re looking to bring a guest for a day or two, they can work out using our day pass option.",
  },
  {
    question: "Is there parking available?",
    answer:
      "We offer plenty of safe parking during our operating hours from 5 am to 10 pm.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you offer personal training services?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we offer personal training sessions. Please refer to our Services page to learn more.",
  },
  {
    question: "What amenities do you offer?",
    answer:
      "All our packages come with access to lockers, showers, and sauna facilities.",
  },
  {
    question: "What payment methods do you accept?",
    answer: "We accept payment through cash and bank transfers.",
  },
];

export const MemberFAQs = [
  {
    question: "What are the membership options available?",
    answer:
      "We offer Individual, Personal Training, and Group Class Training Plans, each available with membership options for 3, 6, and 12 months. For more information, please visit our services section.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you have monthly plans?",
    answer: "No, our membership plans start at 3 months.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I sign up for a membership?",
    answer:
      "To sign up for a membership, you have two convenient options: you can register online and complete payment via bank transfer, or you can visit one of our branches, register at the reception, and complete payment in person. For online registration details, feel free to reach out to us.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is your cancellation policy?",
    answer:
      "To cancel your membership, please visit the reception in person for further assistance and details.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I freeze or pause my membership?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can freeze your membership when you are sick or are traveling. You can freeze for 14 days on 3-month Memberships, 30 days on 6-month Memberships, and 60 days on 12-month Memberships.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I upgrade or downgrade my membership plan at any time?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can upgrade or downgrade your membership plan at any time. Simply reach out for more details.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between Group Class and Group Class Pro?",
    answer:
      "In the Group Class membership, you can only join scheduled group classes. With the Group Class PRO membership, you have access to both group classes and the gym for individual workouts outside of group class schedules.",
  },
  {
    question: "On the Personal Training Plan, how do I choose a trainer?",
    answer:
      "On the Personal Training Plan, we will match you with a trainer based on your specific goals and schedule.",
  },
];
